Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 2002 Acquisition, 1984-2002, undated; 20.17; (26 boxes)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    - "One Hour at St. Peters", 2001 March; 1; 01:00:10; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362858)
    - "Phoebe Snow + Sapphic Sisters (Sakimura Tribute)", 1999 November 07; 1; 01:34:19 (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362866)
    - "Sapphic Sisters", 1999 December 5; 1; 01:34:11; Sound on the tape is not always clear. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362874)
    - "Sapphic Sisters", 2001 October 28; 1; 01:34:37; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362882)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Writers Workshop: (Ain't Been Sick in a Long Time)", 1999 September 26; 1; 01:34:33; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program was recorded at a low level on the right channel for the first 47 minutes of the tape. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362890)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop", 1999 September; 1; 01:33:28; A warble can be heard at the beginning of the tape. Sound can be heard on top of other audio from 7:27 and throughout the tape. The program is recorded over pre-existing content. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362908)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop" (copy 2), 1999 December; 1; 01:34:12 (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362916)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop", 2000 February 13; 1; 01:34:43; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The right channel decreases in volume over the course of the first 47 minutes. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362924)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop", 2000 March 19; 1; 00:43:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 75, Item barcode 39002099362932)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop Gemini Party" / Earl Pathra Hines, Stan Turrentine, 2000 June 11; 1; 01:19:35; The program was recorded at a very low level at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362940)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop Gratitude Journal", 2000 April 2; 1; 00:57:42; The program is distorted at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362957)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Workshop Great Worksh." / "Blossom", 1999 October 10; 1; 01:34:18 (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362965)
    - "Sapphic Workshop", 1999 September 12; 1; 00:44:55; A warble can be heard on the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362973)
    - "Sapphic Workshop", 2001 July 15; 1; 01:34:51; The program is distorted at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362981)
    - "Sapphic Workshop", 2001 August; 1; 01:33:51 (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099362999)
    - "Sapphic Workshop: Folk Poems", undated; 1; 01:34:02; The program is distorted at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099363005)
    - "Sapphic Writers Workshop", 2001 September 30; 1; 01:33:33; The program is distorted at times. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099363013)
    - "Sapphos", 2001 February; 1; 01:02:30; The program was recorded at a very low level. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099363021)
    - "A voice letter to Michael: Love Linda", 2001 September 22; 1; 00:44:51; High background noise is heard on the tape. (Box 76, Item barcode 39002099363039)
    - " Chiron Review Poetry Festival, St. John, Kansas, film by David James, 1999 August 7-8; YCALMSS836_0014; 1; 01:57:24; This tape is of very poor quality. There is a time and date stamp throughout the video. (Box 77, Item barcode 39002102317279)
    - " Chiron Review Poetry Festival, St. John, Kansas, 1999 August 8; ycalmss836_0015; 1; 01:46:33; There is a time and date stamp that runs throughout the video. (Box 77, Item barcode 39002102317287)
    - Kopp, Karl. Infernal Witness: A Play, undated; YCALMSS836_0016; 1; 01:35:53 (Box 77, Item barcode 39002102317295)
    - "San Francisco Lesbian and Gay Parade", 2002; YCALMSS836_0017; 1; 03:11:09 (Box 77, Item barcode 39002102317303)
      At the end of the tape, part of an episode of "I Love Lucy" runs for about 14 minutes.
  - Other Papers
    - "5 A.M." (Box 64)
    - "Theatre 150" (Box 64)
    - "Beyond Baroque" (Box 64)
    - "Norman Olson" (Box 64)
    - Board minutes, 1984 (Box 65)
    - "Art" (Box 65)
    - "Flier Masters" (Box 65)
    - "Ads" (Box 65)
    - Accounts and receipts, 4 (Box 64)
    - Lists of addresses, 5 (Box 65)
    - Lists of addresses, 7 (Box 64)
    - Mailing lists (Box 65)
    - "Filled Purchase Orders" (Box 65)
    - "Next C.R." (Box 65)
    - "Filed P.O.s" (Box 65)
    - "Form Rejection Letters" (Box 65)
    - "Copyright" (Box 65)
    - "ISBN" (Box 65)
    - "Library of Congress" (Box 65)
    - "Censorship" (Box 65)
    - "TV Poetry Show" (Box 65)
    - "Alternative Printers" (Box 65)
    - "Reviewers Guidelines" (Box 65)
    - "Rate Cards" (Box 65)
    - "Exchange Ads" (Box 65)
    - "Clip Art" (Box 65)
    - "Ingram Periodicals", 4 (Box 65)
    - "Rejected Submissions", 4 (Box 65)
    - "Poets' Visions" (Box 65)
    - "TV Poetry Show" (Box 65)
    - "Why the System Must be Changed" (Box 65)
    - "Lyn Lifshin" (Box 65)
    - "Production" (Box 65)
    - "Flyers" (Box 65)
    - "2/13/82", 3 (Box 65)
    - Office supplies (Box 65)
    - Photographs, 9 (Box 65)
    - The Kindred Spirit / Chiron Review index (card file) (Box 66)
    - The Kindred Spirit / Chiron Review index (card file) (Box 67)
    - Office supplies (Box 69)
    - Poster (Box 73 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook (Box 73 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook (Box 74 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified, 22 (Box 68)
    - Unidentified, 10 3.5 inch computer disks
      - MSN on-line community 2nd chat - June 6, 2002 Cait Collins (OH) + Connie Star (KS) mjh, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0048; 1 (Box 78)
      - Blue Dots computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0049; 1 (Box 78)
      - Starry Night Computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0050; 1 (Box 78)
      - Lotsa Lines computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0051; 1 (Box 78)
      - Sun computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0052; 1 (Box 78)
      - Rainbow Chaos computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0053; 1 (Box 78)
      - Fruit and Window computer art by Michael Hathaway 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0054; 1 (Box 78)
      - Pan and Friend computer art by Michael Hathaway 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0055; 1 (Box 78)
      - Blue Sun computer art by Michael Hathaway 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0056; 1 (Box 78)
      - Spatula computer art by Michael Hathaway, 2001, 2002-ycal-1107-ac-0057; 1 (Box 78)
- March 2006 Acquisition, 1985-2006, undated; 16.33; (26 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Boxes 100 and 103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Hirst, Barbara, 3 (Box 79)
    - Hornack, Nicholas (Box 79)
    - McDaniel, Wilma Elizabeth, 2 (Box 79)
    - Unsorted, 2002 October-2003 December; 35 (Box 79)
    - Unsorted, 2003 December-2005 March; 33 (Box 80)
    - Unsorted, 2005 March-December; 26 (Box 81)
    - Unsorted (e-mail), 2002-2005; 22 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Chiron Review letters 2002, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0032; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 05/01/04-06/29/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0064; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail 11/18-03 --, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0070; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron e-mail corr. 10/3/2003-11/18/03 fic, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0071; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence Sept. 27, 2002 - Jan. 16, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0072; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review correspondence Jan. 17, 2003 - Feb. 10, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0073; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence 2/16/03- 2/26/03, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0074; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence Feb. 16, 2003 - Apr. 14, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0075; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence Feb. 10-Mar.? 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0076; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence April 15, 2003-June 18, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0077; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence June 19 - Aug. 17, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0078; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence Aug. 18-Oct. 3, 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0079; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 2/3/04-2/15/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0080; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 2/14/04-3/24/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0081; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 03/25/04-04/30/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0082; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 06/29/04-8/26/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0083; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 08/30/04-11/26/2004, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0084; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail corr. 11/29/2004-02/16/2005 mjh, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0085; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review Letters Aug. 4, 2002-March 12, 2005, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0086; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail correspondence Feb. 16, 2005 - May 2005 emails May-aug. 14, 2005 lost., 2006-ycal-0327-o-0087; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail aug. 15, 2005 - 11/22/05 (emails May-aug. 14, 2005 lost), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0088; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review e-mail Nov. 23, 2005 --, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0113; 1 (Box 104)
    - Unsorted (e-mail), 2003 November-2004 February; 1 CD
      - Chiron Review em: 11/18/2003 Jo 2/2/04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0110; 1 (Box 105)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Chiron Review 71 (2003 summer), 8 (Box 81)
    - Chiron Review 71 (2003 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #71 summer 2003, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0089; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 71 (2003 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 90 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 72 (2003 autumn), 9 (Box 82)
    - Chiron Review 72 (2003 autumn), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #72, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0090; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 73 (2003 winter), 8 (Box 82)
    - Chiron Review 73 (2003 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #73 (winter 2003) mjh, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0091; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 73 (2003 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 90 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 74 (2004 spring), 7 (Box 82)
    - Chiron Review 74 (2004 spring), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #74 spring 2004, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0092; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 75 (2004 summer), 9 (Box 83)
    - Chiron Review 75 (2004 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR 75 summer 2004 mjh, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0093; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 76 (2004 autumn), 7 (Box 83)
    - Chiron Review 76 (2004 autumn), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #76 autumn 2004, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0094; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 76 (2004 autumn) (mechanicals) (Box 91 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 77 (2004 winter), 9 (Box 83)
    - Chiron Review 77 (2004 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #77 winter 2004, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0095; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 78 (2005 spring), 9 (Box 84)
    - Chiron Review 78 (2005 spring), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - Chiron Review #78, spring 2005 (Northup), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0096; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 78 (2005 spring) (mechanicals) (Box 91 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 79 (2005 summer), 10 (Box 84)
    - Chiron Review 79 (2005 summer), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #79 summer 2005 Wanda Coleman, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0097; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 79 (2005 summer) (mechanicals), 2 (Box 92 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 80 (2005 autumn), 9 (Box 85)
    - Chiron Review 80 (2005 autumn), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #80 autumn, 2005, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0098; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review 80 (2005 autumn) (mechanicals) (Box 92 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 81 (2005 winter), 14 (Box 85)
    - Chiron Review 81 (2005 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disk
      - CR #81 11/5/05, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0099; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (mechanicals) (Box 93 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review. Unidentified (mechanicals), 2 (Box 94 (Oversize))
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - Diary. "Favorite Poems" (Box 85)
    - Diary, 1985 - 2005 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1993-1996 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1995 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1996 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1996-1997 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1997 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1997-1998 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 1999 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 2001 (Box 86)
    - Diary, 2003-2004 (Box 95 (Oversize))
    - Diary, 2004 (Box 86)
    - Cosmic Children: Collected Kittens and Cats, 2005; 3 (Box 87)
    - Epistle, 3 (Box 87)
    - Unidentified, with related correspondence, 12 (Box 87)
  - Other Writings
    - Brown, Juanita. "Praise: Elegies for a New Millenium", 3 (Box 87)
    - Burger, Reuben. "Broken Rearview Mirror" and short biography, 1 CD
      - Reuben Burger 'Broken Rearview Mirror' and Short Bio, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0102; 1 (Box 105)
    - Catlin, Alan. "Thou Shalt Not Kill" (Box 87)
    - Catlin, Alan. "Thou Shalt Not Kill", 1 3.5 inch disk
      - MS - THOU SHALT NOT KILL ALAN CATLIN 143 Furman Street Schenectady, NY 12304, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0116; 1 (Box 104)
    - Chorlton, David. "A Normal Day Amazes Us", 4 (Box 87)
    - Clutter, Tyrus. "Digital Portfolio", 1 CD
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0327-o-0112; 1 (Box 105)
    - Culleton, Terence. "Message from A Floating Dock" (Box 87)
    - Duhamel, Denise. Unidentified, 1 CD
      - Denise Duhamel, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0108; 1 (Box 105)
    - Estable, Luis A. Unidentfied poetry (Box 87)
    - Flannery, Leslie. "Smelly Girl", 2 (Box 87)
    - Flannery, Leslie. "Smelly Girl", 1 CD
      - Smelly Girl c 2005 FLANNERY, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0103; 1 (Box 105)
    - Holt, Olga G. and Holt, Rochelle Lynn. "With Promises to Keep", 2004; 9 (Box 87)
    - Huntsinger, Barbara. "Black & White Paper Roses" (Box 88)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Cuba Diary", 2 (Box 88)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon, editor. "Unexpected Harvest", 4 (Box 88)
    - Korb, Albert B. "ALB-Peace King Y Queen of the Gods" (Box 88)
    - Kruse, Kent. Unidentified (Box 88)
    - Kruse, Kent. "Esurk's Nightmare" (Box 88)
    - Kruse, Kent. "A Fruit Cake Only A Mother Could Love" (Box 88)
    - Kruse, Kent. "Oh When the Saints Come Marching In" (Box 88)
    - Kruse, Kent. "The Walls of Stanley's Mind" (Box 88)
    - Long, Virginia Love. "Lord Byron's Civet" (Box 88)
    - Long, Virginia Love. "Spider Woman", 2 (Box 88)
    - Lyons, Larry D. "Freudian Dream Interpretation for Poets", 2 (Box 88)
    - Mix, Larry. "Historical Postcards: Stafford County, Kansas. 1st, Unofficial draft", 2002 August; 1 CD
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0327-o-0107; 1 (Box 105)
    - Montclair. "Works in Progress; Co-features Beth Elliott, Kaylah Marin; Host: Cindy Geiser", 2006 Jan 03; 1 DVD-RW
      - WIP 1/06 Zeiser, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0111; 1 (Box 105)
    - Nel. "Remaining Oceans", 1 CD
      - MIKE - PLEASE USE THIS CD. CONTAINS REVISED BIO PLUS REMAINING OCEANS WITH ADDED LINE PLUS THE OTHER THREE POEMS -THANKS Nel, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0109; 1 (Box 105)
    - Rimbaud, Dee. Unidentified (Box 88)
    - Rimbaud, Dee. Unidentified, 1 CD
      - ARTWORK DEE RIMBAUD E-mail: deerimbaud@hotmail.com, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0104; 1 (Box 105)
    - Schulze, Michael. "Love Song" (Box 88)
    - Stern, L. "A White Light Season Lightly Biography", 1 CD
      - a White Light Season Lightly Biography L. Stern, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0106; 1 (Box 105)
    - Tener, Rober L. "The Door to Summer" (Box 88)
    - Tener, Robert L. "Let the Dark Catch Us", 2 (Box 88)
    - Watson, Maurice, Jr. "Miscellanea" (Box 88)
    - Watson, Maurice, Jr. "New Beginnings" (Box 88)
    - Watson, Maurice, Jr. "A Review, Some Poems, and an Essay" (Box 88)
    - Watson, Maurice, JR. "Rick's Place" (Box 88)
    - Watson, Maurice T., Jr. "Truth IV", 2 (Box 88)
    - Wilgus, Neal. "Rhymed and Dangerous" (Box 88)
    - Unidentified, 9 (Box 88)
    - Unidentified, 62 3.5 inch computer disks
      - David W. Caruthers P.O. Box 2337 Easton, MD 21601 in service Bio Word Files fic, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0001; 1 (Box 104)
      - MICHAEL- HERE ARE MY TWO POEMS. THANKS! -j., 2006-ycal-0327-o-0002; 1 (Box 104)
      - RYAN ROWE FOR CHIRON 71, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0003; 1 (Box 104)
      - George Drew, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0004; 1 (Box 104)
      - HARDIN 3 poems Word (PC), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0005; 1 (Box 104)
      - Migliore poe, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0006; 1 (Box 104)
      - Russell Powell 413-247-3232 "Lust" "Still Life", 2006-ycal-0327-o-0007; 1 (Box 104)
      - Will Nixon 2 poems unusable, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0011; 1 (Box 104)
      - Curt Last -Leaving for Guam -Tale of the Soiled Mattress -Patpong Night Market, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0012; 1 (Box 104)
      - RUTH MOON KEMPHER FoundPoem: Favorite Clowns + Detritus [Trash] Pm, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0013; 1 (Box 104)
      - Bruce Spang -Review -Poems, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0014; 1 (Box 104)
      - R. Wexelblatt Poems: I Keep to Myself and Blue Flu (+ bio note), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0015; 1 (Box 104)
      - PANDORA'S BOX as submitted to Christina Zimmerman at PublishAmerica.com April 30, 2004, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0016; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review 1) #2 2)# #3 3) #5 4) ellipsis 5) BIO Sarah Daugherty 06 Hollywood Witch Girl Power, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0017; 1 (Box 104)
      - Elvira Bennet What Mrs. Podolski Believes In (poem) + Bio Note, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0018; 1 (Box 104)
      - Harry E. Northup Interview Word2000 for P.C. copyright 2004 b Reynold Akison, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0019; 1 (Box 104)
      - DAVID CHORLTON Brief Light, Purpose, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0020; 1 (Box 104)
      - Playing the Hazards by D. N. Baldwin, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0021; 1 (Box 104)
      - Wesley Clark, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0022; 1 (Box 104)
      - LUCKY WAY HEMINGWAY BIO McWade, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0023; 1 (Box 104)
      - NELSON JAMES DUNFORD "A Sacrificial Panda on 14 February" + Brief Bio, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0024; 1 (Box 104)
      - HUGH FOX Review of Kiot (Potts), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0025; 1 (Box 104)
      - Unexpected Harvest 03/10/05, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0026; 1 (Box 104)
      - RONALD BAATZ, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0027; 1 (Box 104)
      - OIDLINES Sheila Cowing, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0028; 1 (Box 104)
      - The Indaria Shop Cooperman, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0029; 1 (Box 104)
      - Hutner. War: A Book of Poems Review by William A. Suffans, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0030; 1 (Box 104)
      - ALAN CATLIN 143 Furman Street Schenectady, NY 12304, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0031; 1 (Box 104)
      - translating 4 cat stories MH only 05/07/03, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0034; 1 (Box 104)
      - Tenderness in HELL Disk #1, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0035; 1 (Box 104)
      - Michael Meyerhofer "The Oldest Religion" "Republican Parents", 2006-ycal-0327-o-0036; 1 (Box 104)
      - photo of Edward Field jpeg + bitmap, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0038; 1 (Box 104)
      - James Benedict: 20/X-03 Review of Clifton Snider, The Alchemy of Opposites Jamesbenedict777@hotmail.com, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0039; 1 (Box 104)
      - WILLIAM SHELDON "SODIUM + GOMER" (and bio.) MICROSOFT WORD 2000 sheldon@sctelcom.net (620) 662-8632, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0040; 1 (Box 104)
      - watchdialpm.doc RMK WhtDogsNopm.doc BigBellyPm2.doc (Translations!) Hieroglyppm.doc Motorcyclespm.doc Brebiofmm, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0041; 1 (Box 104)
      - Chiron Review Linda Rochelew interview poems subcrptions, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0043; 1 (Box 104)
      - ROBERT COHEN 1691 STARK AVE. COOS BAY, OR 97420 (541) 888-3177 bobzcohen@yahoo.com, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0044; 1 (Box 104)
      - ZYDEK TO CHIRON REVIEW (PHOTO-BIO-POEMS) poe, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0045; 1 (Box 104)
      - Ian Grey "The Wanderer" author photo bio, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0046; 1 (Box 104)
      - Amy Spade poems + bio, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0047; 1 (Box 104)
      - Tom Schmidlin Submission For Chiron Review, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0048; 1 (Box 104)
      - 11/11/03 CHIRON RYAN ROWE AD, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0049; 1 (Box 104)
      - "WRINKLES" + bio Microsoft Word Tony Báez Milán/P.O. Box 931221 Los Angeles/CA/90093, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0050; 1 (Box 104)
      - ANIS SHIVANI: "LIFE OF PI" REVIEW. 08/22/03 (713) 981-4301 ANIS_SHIVANI_AB92 @ POST.HARVARD.EDU, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0051; 1 (Box 104)
      - Michael Hoerman Poems + bio, 2 versions-- in Word 2000 + Word 2.0 B+W as jpg, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0052; 1 (Box 104)
      - "Archipelago" by Steve Sherwood Word files fic, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0053; 1 (Box 104)
      - Amanda Braumanking "The Blue Room" + bio 11/2003 PC DISK RTF Files, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0055; 1 (Box 104)
      - Harriet Miller Sparrow revised 10/10/07, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0056; 1 (Box 104)
      - Lesliee 11/12/03, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0057; 1 (Box 104)
      - Shane Jones Chiron Review 3 poems, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0058; 1 (Box 104)
      - The Quick of Scent E.M. SCHORB, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0059; 1 (Box 104)
      - 2 Basinski reviews, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0060; 1 (Box 104)
      - Doug Riston Chiron Review, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0061; 1 (Box 104)
      - MS WORD REDEMPTION, CHPT TWO (OR "FUCKING" OR WHATEVER) Robert L. Penick 3929 S. Fifth Street Louisville, KY 40214, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0062; 1 (Box 104)
      - Ron Androla poems (Erie PA) 2001-2002, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0063; 1 (Box 104)
      - not Mac Sward interview pliura etc. Toys.99 (CHIRON) Journal 8/9-2000 mjh tony Sheila MacAvoy Block P.O.Box 1259 Santa Barbara, CA 93102, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0065; 1 (Box 104)
      - The Night After I Helped to Kill a Man Joan Jobe Smith, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0067; 1 (Box 104)
      - Modified story 4/27/05 John Cole 15834 26th Ave. NE Seattle, WA 98155, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0068; 1 (Box 104)
      - GUS Virginia Lone Long 9/24/99, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0100; 1 (Box 104)
      - #105 cosmic last three files of final, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0101; 1 (Box 104)
      - Careful! Moon Horses Squirrel Girls piano by Gary Every PO Box 5419 Oracle AZ 85623 saved under Microsoft Word, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0114; 1 (Box 104)
      - Forbidden Tricks (fictionwise ebooks, 2005) by Alexander Renault (aka Nick Hornack.), 2006-ycal-0327-o-0115; 1 (Box 104)
    - Unidentified, 1 CD
      - Ad Marginem & Bio., 2006-ycal-0327-o-0101; 1 (Box 105)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 100-101, 102 (Record album storage), and box 103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "A & B [Sapphic] Sisters Writers Workshop, sun in sag...moon in Leo", November 24; 1; 01:34:05; The sound is not always clear on the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363047)
    - "JAR" A1-A10 Spiel / "JAR" B11-B14 Spiel, undated; 1; 00:56:23 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363054)
      A note found with this audiocassette reads: Michael, True to my word - I've promised several times that I would send you a sample of me reading from my new collection, "JAR". Well, here 'tis! These pieces are still being worked on but are far enough along to present. Hope you find them interesting listening...Spiel.
    - "Montclair Women's Center", 2004 March; 1; 01:34:29; A warble can be heard throughout the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363062)
    - "Sapphic Sisters Writers Workshop, Gemini", 2003 June; 1; 01:01:07; The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363070)
    - "Sapphos, Folk Poems!", 2003 September 28; 1; 01:00:56; High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363088)
    - "St. Peter's and S.L. Healthcare / Rev. Franklin & Linda", 2002 September 27; 1; 01:34:46; The program is distorted at times. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002099363096)
    - "Beyond Birds Beneath the Wailing"
      - "Beyond birds beneath the wailing" <C Lish THUMB2> 8 min 48 sec. HOME DUMMY SPIEL 9/26, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0117; 1 (Box 101)
    - "Looking At the Floor"
      - looking at the floor X 4 min 50 sec Spiel home dummy, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0118; 1 (Box 101)
    - "Spiel, Mania, 2005 Sep 6"
      - SPIEL X HOME 3 min 38 sec "Mania" 9.6.05 Dummy, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0119; 1 (Box 101)
    - "The Skinning"